William Z Chadwick - Web Developer



- About Me

William Z Chadwick is a father of four, a critical and creative thinker, a language learner, code learner, and has worked in just about every industry there is, from construction, furniture delivery, to caregiving for the elderly, summer camps, the special needs community, and tutoring.

With a mix of intensity and care, of thoughtfulness and resourcefulness --coming at problems from many different angles, with input and



Graphic Designer

Training -

Udemy Courses

Bash Mastery: Complete Guide to Bash Shell Scripting, 70%

C++: From Beginning to Beyond, 33% Git and Github Bootcamp, 100%

Brief Guide to Business Continuity & Disaster Recovery, 60%

The Odin Project

Foundations Course, 44%

Mimo

Web Development, 100% Python3, 100% SQL Course, 100%

Grasshopper

Foundations I, 100% Foundations II, 100% Intro to Interviewing, 80%

LinkedIn Learning

Bash Shell Scripting for Automation, 100%

- Work History

HCTI

Delivery Associate 2021 - Present

Caregiver

Morning Star Sentior Living **Bonaventure of CastleRock** 2018-2020

Academic Mentor

TutorDoctor + OBU Student Success Center + Private Tutor 2013-2015 & 2018-2021





- Education

Promineo Tech

Front End Bootcamp HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootsrap, React, Mocha/Chai,

Oklahoma Baptist University

Major: English

Minor: Graphic Design From 2011 to 2015

(I am 3 courses away from graduating)